School of Dental Medicine Records UA020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, artifacts, and videos, 1910 -- 2020; UA020.003; 21.17 Linear Feet 16 oversized boxes and oversized folders in a map case.; 44 Digital Object(s)
  - Dental School class picture, 1986; UA020.000207; 1 Digital Object(s); 134 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1987; UA020.000208; 1 Digital Object(s); 151 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1987; UA020.000209; 1 Digital Object(s); 108 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1988; UA020.000210; 1 Digital Object(s); 164 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1988; UA020.000211; 1 Digital Object(s); 82.2 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1989; UA020.000212; 1 Digital Object(s); 162 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1989; UA020.000213; 1 Digital Object(s); 141 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1990; UA020.000214; 1 Digital Object(s); 153 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1990; UA020.000215; 1 Digital Object(s); 141 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1991; UA020.000216; 1 Digital Object(s); 133 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1991; UA020.000217; 1 Digital Object(s); 147 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School Transfer class picture, 1991; UA020.000218; 1 Digital Object(s); 129 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1992; UA020.000219; 1 Digital Object(s); 144 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1992; UA020.000220; 1 Digital Object(s); 103 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School Transfer class picture, 1992; UA020.000221; 1 Digital Object(s); 125 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1993; UA020.000222; 1 Digital Object(s); 212 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1993; UA020.000223; 1 Digital Object(s); 98.1 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1994; UA020.000224; 1 Digital Object(s); 209 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1994; UA020.000225; 1 Digital Object(s); 102 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1995; UA020.000226; 1 Digital Object(s); 215 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1995; UA020.000227; 1 Digital Object(s); 104 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1996; UA020.000228; 1 Digital Object(s); 216 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1996; UA020.000229; 1 Digital Object(s); 118 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 1997; UA020.000230; 1 Digital Object(s); 218 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School class picture, 1998; UA020.000231; 1 Digital Object(s); 220 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School class picture, 1999; UA020.000232; 1 Digital Object(s); 228 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1999; UA020.000233; 1 Digital Object(s); 126 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Dental School class picture, 2000; UA020.000234; 1 Digital Object(s); 225 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2001; UA020.000235; 1 Digital Object(s); 234 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2002; UA020.000236; 1 Digital Object(s); 228 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2003; UA020.000237; 1 Digital Object(s); 217 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2004; UA020.000238; 1 Digital Object(s); 217 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2005; UA020.000239; 1 Digital Object(s); 120 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2006; UA020.000240; 1 Digital Object(s); 120 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2007; UA020.000241; 1 Digital Object(s); 224 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2008; UA020.000242; 1 Digital Object(s); 222 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2009; UA020.000243; 1 Digital Object(s); 228 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Advanced and Graduate Education Dental School class picture, 2016; UA020.000244; 1 Digital Object(s); 41.1 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2017; UA020.000245; 1 Digital Object(s); 43 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2018; UA020.000246; 1 Digital Object(s); 42.6 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Dental School class picture, 2020; UA020.000247; 1 Digital Object(s); 43.9 Megabytes (Box 10)
- Student theses, dissertations, papers, 1930 -- 1963; UA020.004; 23 Volumes
  This series contains student theses, dissertations, and papers.
  This series is arranged chronologically by type of paper.
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class, 1936; UA020.004.011.001 (Volume 11)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (A-G), 1937; UA020.004.012.001 (Volume 12)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (A-H), 1938; UA020.004.013.001 (Volume 13)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (H-W), 1937; UA020.004.014.001 (Volume 14)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (A-W), 1938; UA020.004.015.001 (Volume 15)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (L-Z), 1938; UA020.004.016.001 (Volume 16)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class, 1939; UA020.004.017.001 (Volume 17)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class, 1940; UA020.004.018.001 (Volume 18)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (A-L), 1941; UA020.004.019.001 (Volume 19)
  - Operative Dentistry Essays; Junior Dental Class (M-Z), 1941; UA020.004.020.001 (Volume 20)
  - Theses; ETA SIGMA SIGMA & R.R.A, 1930 -- 1934; UA020.004.021.001 (Volume 21)
  - Theses; ETA SIGMA SIGMA & R.R.A, 1935 -- 1938; UA020.004.022.001 (Volume 22)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine; Research Papers, 1947 -- 1950; UA020.004.023.001 (Volume 23)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine; Research Papers, 1951 -- 1956; UA020.004.024.001 (Volume 24)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine; Research Papers, 1957 -- 1960; UA020.004.025.001 (Volume 25)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine; Research Papers, 1961 -- 1963; UA020.004.026.001 (Volume 26)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1935; UA020.004.027.001 (Volume 27)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1937; UA020.004.028.001 (Volume 28)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1938; UA020.004.029.001 (Volume 29)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1939; UA020.004.030.001 (Volume 30)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1940; UA020.004.031.001 (Volume 31)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1941; UA020.004.032.001 (Volume 32)
  - Peridontia Papers; Senior Dental Class, 1942; UA020.004.033.001 (Volume 33)
- Additional accessions, UA020.000133
  - Tufts School of Dental Medicine, UA020-002 (Box 1)
    - Homecoming "Save the Date" brochure, 2017; UA020-003-00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Tufts School of Dental Medicine, miscellaneous, 1939 -- 1986; UA020-001 (Box 2)
  - Publications, minutes and syllabus, 1910 -- 2014; UA020-003 (Box 3)
    Tufts Dental Outlook; Tufts Dental Club of New York Bulletin; Dentufts; Dentech; Class Record; Omicron Kappa Upsilon meeting minutes; Syllabus of lecture on histology - 1910; TUSDM Continuing Education 2013-2014; issues of Journal of the Massachusetts Dental Society, 2013-2014, featuring TUSDM faculty.
- 2020 accessions, circa 2002 -- 2017; UA020.000136; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  This series contains records from the School of Dental Medicine Development and Alumni Relations Office, including publications related to the Beyond Boundaries campaign, Vertical Expansion Initiative, and other School of Dental Medicine events.
  - Development and Alumni Relations records, circa 2002 -- 2017; UA020.000137 (Box 1)
    This box contains some restricted material and may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
    Publications, printed and digital photographs on CD-R, and DVDs related to the Beyond Boundaries campaign, Vertical Expansion Initiative, and other School of Dental Medicine events.
- 2023 Accessions, 1956 -- 2015; UA020.000248; 1 Linear Feet
  This series contains records of Professor Hilde Tillman's research, teaching, and work with the Geriatric Dentistry Program at Tufts, dating from 1956 to 2015.